{
    "subject": "resource/The_Automatic",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Yourcodenameis:milo",
    "human_readable": "The Automatic is associated with Yourcodenameis:milo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9797882437705994,
            "question": "Is there a connection between The Automatic and Yourcodenameis:milo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9443635940551758,
            "question": "What is associated with Yourcodenameis:milo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9388158917427063,
            "question": "How are The Automatic and Yourcodenameis:milo connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9125418066978455,
            "question": "Are there any other known associations with Yourcodenameis:milo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8395630717277527,
            "question": "Is there anything else related to Yourcodenameis:milo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41569116711616516,
            "question": "Who or what is The Automatic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3670457601547241,
            "question": "What does The Automatic do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31898418068885803,
            "question": "Can you elaborate on The Automatic's role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23462508618831635,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about The Automatic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07353799790143967,
            "question": "What is the significance of this association?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Automatic is associated with Yourcodenameis:milo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5040_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about The Automatic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5040_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you elaborate on The Automatic's role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5040_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does The Automatic do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5040_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5040_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Paul Mullen from Yourcodenameis:milo joined The Automatic in 2007, and that the two bands collaborated on various projects. Specifically, it mentions that Mullen became a vocalist, guitarist, and keys/synthesizer player for The Automatic after a mutual friend suggested he join the band, and that they worked together to write tracks such as \"Trapeze Artist\" from their Print is Dead collaboration album."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Paul Mullen from Yourcodenameis:milo joined The Automatic, indicating an association between the two."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}